Hi everyone, in this video we're going to chat a little bit about webcam and
also about what you
might say or do on your first time when you go online. Okay so let's start by
chatting about
the basics of what to actually do when you first go online. Firstly I would
recommend taking up as
much of the screen as possible so being nice and close to the camera. That way
of course your
clients can see you properly. So when you've got your first call just take a
deep breath, relax,
answer the call, with a smile you can ask them hey how are you, how's your day
being or you can
even have a story in your head that you've made up that you want to speak about
on cam. So for
example you might not know where to take the conversation so you could have a
story in your
head that could be maybe the mailman came around today and the mailman was
really hot and it made
you feel a sit and type away and you can chat to your clients about this. It
might just sound like
a random little story and it obviously can be made up too but this will help
the conversation get
flowing and then take you on to the next part of the conversation wherever that
may be and it's
literally just something just to break the ice and just to get the convo
started and then of course
you can take the congo in any direction you want after that. If you don't
really feel to make up
a story you can always just ask them how their day is being and then just see
where it goes from
there. Something that I personally like to do is to ask the clients so what
brings you into my chat
room today and that way we can gauge if it's actually a client that we want to
come with or not
because maybe they're going to say that they want to do something that you're
not comfortable with
or that you don't offer. For example they might say oh I just want someone to
dominate me today
and maybe that's not something that you do so then you can just politely let
the client know that
maybe they should look for somebody else on the website as you don't offer this
or maybe they will say something that you don't actually offer usually but it's
something that you
want to try so then this is the perfect opportunity to try this. Okay so
something else that you want
to take into consideration is your webcam setup so by this I mean the quality
of your webcam
the lighting and the space around you so you want to make sure that the quality
of your webcam is
of high standard and the lighting too as if the clients can't actually see you
properly it doesn't
matter how good you look they're not going to come back and this also goes for
your webcam setup so
you want the space that you're coming in to be really inviting to the clients
and you can even
place things around the room that might draw them in for example you might have
some props
that you use on come in the background so they can see them and then their mind
will start to wonder
about if you're actually going to use them in session with them. You can also
think about getting
a wireless keyboard so if you're on a bed or you know even on the couch or
whatever you can sit
favour back and have your keyboard next to you rather than having to be up close
to the webcam
I do think it is good to be close to the screen when you first start coming
when you're first
in those initial few minutes of the chat but then maybe depending on where the
conversation goes
you know they might want your whole body in viewing the webcam so then you can
come a little bit favour back and use the wireless keyboard for this
I would also like to chat a little bit about the wrong assumptions when it
comes to webcam
so people on the outside have ideas of how it is and what webcam is and to be
honest it's never
right it's never true because nobody truly knows what it's like unless you're
actually doing it
yourself. Many people think that to be a camera is all you have to just do
explicit stuff online
and you know do porn like stuff on there which of course is an element to it if
you want it to be
but that's not all it is and you can make money doing many other things on
there so please don't
let yourself get caught up in a negative stigma that surrounds this industry as
webcam modelling
is literally just somebody who opens their laptop logs online and comes with
clients for money
that's literally all it is but you can decide how you do it and what direction
you take your
campus owner in and to be honest what the clients want can be many different
things
some clients want a sexual chat some clients want a connection some clients
just want some humor
and some banter where there's others may want to be dominated there are many
different things on
there that the clients are into and a lot of clients are into fetish type stuff
as well as they
don't like to explore this in their normal lives so this is why they have this
fantasy on webcam to
be able to explore a lot of their weird and wonderful fetishes so there is a
long list of things you
can do on there so do not let the negative stigma of what people say webcam is
don't let that get
to you because it's completely different to what people think I would like to
end this video by
saying good luck for your first time one calm I'm sure you're going to be
amazing if you just relax
breathe smile and be yourself that's half of the work already done and in time
you'll start to
really know how you want to present yourself on cam maybe you are being
completely yourself or
maybe you have a character in your head that you've made up that you're playing
every single time
you go online which can be quite fun as well and we also have many training
videos on the website
that will help you decide what type of campersona you want to have and also
just help you with
many different things on cam so please take full use of the trainer and I will
see you in the next
video